ngohq.com 2007-04-26

# ATI Radeon Catalyst HD2900 X1950 X1900 X1650 NVIDIA GeForce ForceWare 8800 8600 7950 7900 - NGOHQ.com

**Disclaimer**

**Online-contents**  
The author reserves the right not to be responsible for the topicality, correctness, completeness or quality of the information provided. Liability claims regarding damage caused by the use of any information provided, including any kind of information which is incomplete or incorrect, will therefore be rejected. All offers are not-binding and without obligation. Parts of the pages or the complete publication including all offers and information might be extended, changed or partly or completely deleted by the author without separate announcement.

**Referrals and links**  
The Author is not responsible for any contents linked or referred to from his pages - unless he has full knowlegde of illegal contents and would be able to prevent the visitors of his site from viewing those pages. If any damage occurs by the use of information presented there, only the author of the respective pages might be liable, not the one who has linked to these pages. Furthermore the author is not liable for any postings or messages published by users of discussion boards, guestbooks or mailinglists provided on his page.

**Legal force of this disclaimer**  
This disclaimer is to be regarded as part of the internet publication which you were referred from. If sections or individual formulations of this text are not legal or correct, the content or validity of the other parts remain uninfluenced by this fact. We reserve the right to modify this document without any notice.

**Link to files**  
We don´t allow to link to our files directly. Please link to our download archive or to our mainpage.

**Hostility**  
We reserve our rights to ban any user that shows hostility towards NGOHQ.com, to protect our forums from possible troublemakers. NGOHQ.com is offering all its services for free and we will not tolerate any kind of disrespect. If will feel that the user is a threat to our forums, we may ban and remove user’s access. 

Bashing and hostility towards NGOHQ.com (even on other sites) may results in a permanent ban. Treat us in the way, you wanted to be treated. We reserve our rights to ban anyone that may not fit, this is our website after all and we want to keep it clean and friendly. 

**Privacy Policy**

**Consumer Information**  
During the process of delivering an ad to you, NGOHQ.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, NGOHQ.com does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates (an example would be the customer login). A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to type in a username more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in most areas of our site. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

**Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on NGOHQ.com are delivered to users by our advertising partners. Information about users such as number of times they have viewed an ad is used to serve ads to users on this site. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers, affiliates, or 3rd party sites.

**Links**  
NGOHQ.com contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email address). Contact information will NOT be sent to 3rd party's but only for us to notify the winners and award prizes. Anonymous Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior choice.

**Security**  
This web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line On our site we have programs implemented to protect your email address in our forums. The only way that your email will be publicly avaliable is if you choose to "show" your email address in our forums so other users can contact you. On the Internet there are "Spam Bots", which surf the Internet and collect every email address they find and place them in a database, then they send junk email to all of these users. We have taken it a step higher in security and have blocked spam bots from our site.

**Illegal activity and Press reasons**  
In case you have broken the law, we will have the right to publish your IP address – for legal and professional reasons. NGOHQ.com is a member of the press, and we will publish/share your IP address only due to press reasons and legal reasons. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy or disclaimer, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

 **Downloads**

**License Agreement**  
The software available here from NGOHQ.com are provided "as is" with NO TECHNICAL SUPPORT. All software is to be used at your own risk; this site does not take any responsibility for any damage in whatever form or context. The materials on this Website ("WEBSITE") are provided by NGOHQ.com as a service to its users and may be used for informational purposes only. You may not copy, modify, sublicense, or distribute the downloaded software except as expressly provided under this License. Any attempt otherwise to copy, modify, sublicense or distribute the Program is void, and will automatically terminate your rights under this License. However, parties who have received copies, or rights, from you under this License will not have their licenses terminated so long as such parties remain in full compliance.

All materials available here are provided "as is" with NO TECHNICAL SUPPORT. Under no circumstances, including negligence, shall this WEBSITE be liable for any incidental, special, indirect or consequential damages arising out of or relating to this license and or download. You agree to indemnify and hold this WEBSITE harmless from any and all damages, risk and liabilities. You expressly acknowledge and agree that use of the the downloaded software is at your sole risk. By downloading, installing, copying, or otherwise using the SOFTWARE, you agree to be bound by the terms of this LICENSE. If you do not agree to the terms of this LICENSE, do not download the SOFTWARE.
